Guide to the Arthur and Luce Klein Spoken Arts Records
Yale University Music Library
- Project records, Series I
  - SA872-SA873, SA875: Hans Christian Andersen (vols. II, III, V), 1985 (Box 17, Folder 251)
  - SA873: Hans Christian Andersen (vol. III), 1985 (Box 17, Folder 252)
  - SA874: Hans Christian Andersen (vol. IV), undated (Box 17, Folder 253)
  - SA875: Hans Christian Andersen (vol. V), undated (Box 17, Folder 254)
  - SA876: Hans Christian Andersen (vol. VI), 1963 (Box 17, Folder 255)
  - SA877: Hans Christian Andersen (vol. VII), undated (Box 17, Folder 256)
  - SA878: Rabelais, Francois, Edwards, 1963-1965, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 257)
  - SA879: Dictees Elementaires, undated (Box 17, Folder 258)
    Read by Jean Philippe Gaussens. Includes Photographs.
  - SA881: Henry VIII, 1964, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 259)
  - SA 883: Much Ado About Nothing, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 260)
  - SA884-SA885: The Taming of the Shrew and The Tempest, 1964–1965 (Box 17, Folder 261)
  - SA885: Treasury of Nursery Rhymes (vol. II), 1963 (Box 17, Folder 262)
    Read by Christopher Casson.
  - SA895, SA909: Fables de la Fontaine, 1986, undated (Box 17, Folder 263)
  - SA895: Plus various other SA numbers, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 264)
  - SA902: Lolita, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 265)
  - SA904-SA905: Robert Louis Stevenson, undated (Box 17, Folder 266)
  - SA914: You Know Who and John J. Plenty and Fiddler Dan, 1964-1966, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 267)
    Read by John Ciardi.
  - SA915: President Lydon B. Johnson, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 268)
  - SA916: Lillian Smith, 1965–1966 (Box 17, Folder 269)
  - SA918-SA919: Beowolf, Chaucer -Beowulf, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 270)
  - SA920, SA925: English Fairy Tales (vol. I & II), undated (Box 17, Folder 271)
  - SA924: Jean Vilar in Ses Grands Roles, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 272)
  - SA926: The Death of Patroclus, 1966–1967 (Box 17, Folder 273)
  - SA927: Treasury of Goldsmith, Gray and Collins, undated (Box 17, Folder 274)
  - SA928: Echoes of Greece, undated (Box 17, Folder 275)
  - SA929: Jungle Books by Rudyard Kipling, undated (Box 17, Folder 276)
  - SA940-SA941: Hawthorne, undated (Box 17, Folder 277)
  - SA950: Hyman Kaplan, Production, 1966–1967 (Box 18, Folder 278)
  - SA951
    - The White Seal, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 279)
    - The Jungle Book (vol. III) by Rudyard Kipling, 1966, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 280)
  - SA952
    - The Jungle Book (vol. IV) by Rudyard Kipling, 1966–1967 (Box 18, Folder 281)
    - Plus various other SA numbers, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 282)
  - SA953: Stephen Spender, 1966-1967, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 283)
  - SA954
    The Song of Paul Bunyan and Tony Beaver.
    - Folder 1, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 284)
      Printed copy.
    - Folder 2, 1966–1967 (Box 18, Folder 285)
  - SA955: Fables from Aesop, 1966, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 286)
  - SA956: Ciardi, John, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 287)
  - SA956-SA957: Ciardi, John - This Strangest Everything, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 288)
  - SA958-SA959: She Stoops to Conquer by Oliver Goldsmith, 1966–1967 (Box 18, Folder 289)
  - SA961: The Rape of the Lock, 1966–1967 (Box 18, Folder 290)
    Read by Robert Speaight and Mazine Audley.
  - SA962: Treasury of Alexander Pope, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 291)
  - SA963: Anthology of XIX Century American Poets, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 292)
  - SA964: Strange Fruit by Lillian Smith, 1966–1968 (Box 18, Folder 293)
  - SA965, SA1010: The Rubaiyat of Omar Khayyam, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 294)
  - SA966: The Inaugural Addresses of George Washington, Thomas Jefferson, Abraham Lincoln, Theodore Roosevelt, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 295)
    Read by Senator Goerge McGovern.
  - SA967: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer, 1966-1967, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 296)
  - SA968-SA970: School for Scandal, 1966–1967 (Box 19, Folder 297)
  - SA971-SA972: The Rivals, 1967–1985 (Box 19, Folder 298)
  - SA973: Sonnets from the Portuguese, 1965–1968 (Box 19, Folder 299)
    Read by Penelope Lee.
  - SA974: Treasury of Matthew Arnold, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 300)
  - SA975: Sohrab and Rustum by Matthew Arnold, 1966–1967 (Box 19, Folder 301)
  - SA977: Anthology of Poetry for Children, 1967, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 302)
  - SA978: The Tell-Tale Heart and The Cask of Amontillado by Edgar Allan Poe, 1967–1968 (Box 19, Folder 303)
  - SA979: Mark Twain - The Glorious Whitewasher and Punch, Brother, Punch, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 304)
  - SA980-SA981: Don Juan Tenorio, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 305)
  - SA981: Don Juan Tenorio by Jose Zorrilla, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 306)
    With Spanish text.
  - SA982: Treasury of Bret Harte, 1966-1968, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 307)
    Read by Val Bettin.
  - SA983: Iliad (vol. II) and Odyssey of Homer, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 308)
    Read by Ennis Rees. Includes photographs.
  - SA984: James Dickey Proposed Promotion, 1967-1968, 1970
    - 1 of 3 (Box 20, Folder 309)
    - 2 of 3 (Box 20, Folder 310)
    - 3 of 3 (Box 20, Folder 311)
  - SA984: The Poems of James Dickey, 1967, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 312)
    Includes 2 signed photographs.
  - SA985: Selections of French Literature, 1924, 1987, undated (Box 20, Folder 313)
  - SA985: Heroes, Gods and Monsters of the Greek Legend, 1967–1970 (Box 20, Folder 314)
    Read by Julie Harris and Richard Kiley.
  - SA985: Morceaux Choisis, 1967–1969 (Box 20, Folder 315)
    Read by Madame Jean Provost.
  - SA986: Abba Eban - Address before Security Council, 1967 June 6 (Box 20, Folder 316)
    United Nations, New York, June 6, 1967.
  - SA986-SA987: Abba Eban, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 317)
  - SA987-SA988
    - Abba Eban, 1967–1968 (Box 20, Folder 318)
      Production. Includes photographs.
    - Abba Eban - Address before General Assembly, 1967 June 19 (Box 20, Folder 319)
      United Nations, New York, June 19, 1967.
  - SA989, SA1000-SA1004: Heroes, Gods and Monsters in Greek Myths, 1967–1987 (Box 21, Folder 320)
    Read by Julie Harris and Richard Kiley. Includes Photographs.
  - SA990, 1967–1969
    - Poets for Peace (Box 21, Folder 321)
    - Town Hall Recording - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 21, Folder 322)
  - SA991: The Legend of Sleepy Hallow, 1967-1973, undated (Box 21, Folder 323)
  - SA992: Edgar Allan Poe (Hurd Hatfield), 1963-1970, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 324)
  - SA995: German Poetry, undated (Box 21, Folder 325)
  - SA996: Anais Nin, 1967–1986 (Box 21, Folder 326)
  - SA997: Rip Van Winkle, 1968–1971 (Box 21, Folder 327)
  - SA998: Anthology of German Poetry, 1967–1986
    Read by Alfred Rothschild.
    - 1 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 328)
    - 2 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 329)
  - SA998: Plus Various Other SA Numbers, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 330)
  - SA999: Selected Poems by Wystan Hugh Auden, 1968–1978 (Box 22, Folder 331)
  - SA1003-SA1004, SA1020, SA1063: Madame Widmer, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 332)
  - SA1005
    - Elie Weisel Reading His Works - Letters Concerning Agreement of Elie Weisel, 1967–1987 (Box 22, Folder 333)
    - French Verbs Without Tears, 1972, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 334)
    - Hawthorne, Nathaniel, The Chimaera, undated (Box 22, Folder 335)
  - SA1006
    - O. Henry Stories, 1967-1973, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 336)
    - Plus various other SA numbers, 1985–1986 (Box 22, Folder 337)
  - SA1007
    - Short Stories of Mark Twain, 1967-1970, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 338)
    - Plus various other SA numbers, 1985–1986 (Box 22, Folder 339)
  - SA1008: Adventures of Huckleberry Finn (I), 1968, 1985, undated (Box 22, Folder 340)
  - SA1009: Adventures of Huckleberry Finn (II), 1968 [?], 1985, undated (Box 22, Folder 341)
  - SA1010: Rubaiyat of Omar Khayyam, 1966–1968 (Box 22, Folder 342)
  - SA1010-SA1012: Voices of History, 1969 [?] (Box 22, Folder 343)
  - SA1011-SA1012: Sounds of History, 1966–1968 (Box 22, Folder 344)
    Narrated by Alexnder Scourby.
  - SA1013: The Fables of Aesop, 1968, undated (Box 22, Folder 345)
  - SA1014: Barrack Room Ballads and Other Poems by Rudyard Kipling, 1968, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 346)
  - SA1014, SAC1181, SAC1201: Dr. Martin Luther King, 1961-1962, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 347)
    Correspondence.
  - SA1015: Just So Stories (vol. I), 1968–1972 (Box 22, Folder 348)
  - SA1015-SA1017
    - Just So Stories - Clippings, 1969–1970 (Box 22, Folder 349)
    - Just So Stories - Invoices, 1985–1986 (Box 22, Folder 350)
  - SA1016: Just So Stories (vol. II), 1969 [?] (Box 23, Folder 351)
  - SA1017: Just So Stories (vol. III), 1968–1969 (Box 23, Folder 352)
  - SA1018
    - Robinson Carusoe, 1984 [?]-1985 (Box 23, Folder 353)
    - Plus various other SA numbers, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 354)
  - SA1019: Square That Number, 1967–1971 (Box 23, Folder 355)
  - SA1020: French sans Tears, 1973, undated (Box 23, Folder 356)
  - SA1021: Samuel, Maurice - Reading from His Works, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 357)
  - SA1022: The Speaking of Shakespeare's Verse, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 358)
  - SA1023: Poe, Edgar Allan, The Raven and The Bells, 1968, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 359)
  - SA1024: Captains Courageous, 1969-1970, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 360)
  - SA1025: Treasure Island, 1970, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 361)
  - SA1026: 20,000 Leagues Under the Sea, 1970, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 362)
  - SA1027: Accents, 1968, 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 363)
  - SA1028: The Diary of Samuel Pepys, 1970, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 364)
  - SA1029: Irish Fairy Stories, 1970–1973 (Box 23, Folder 365)
  - SA1030-SA1031: Burrows, Vinie, 1963–1971
    - 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 366)
    - 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 367)
  - SA1032: The Arabian Nights, undated (Box 24, Folder 368)
  - SA1033: The Wind in the Willows, 1969–1973 (Box 24, Folder 369)
  - SA1034: Inaugural Addresses of Lydon Baines Johnson and Richard Milhous Nixon, 1965–1970 (Box 24, Folder 370)
  - SA1035: President Richard Nixon's Eulogy of Eisenhower, 1969–1971 (Box 24, Folder 371)
    Given March 30, 1969.
  - SA1036: The Pilgrim's Progress, 1969-1970, undated (Box 24, Folder 372)
    By John Bunyan.
  - SA1037: Life in Shakespeare's London, 1968-1971, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 373)
  - SA1038: The U.N. Resolution on Racism, 1975–1976
    - 1 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 374)
    - 2 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 375)
  - SA1039: Goldilocks and the Three Bears, Hereinafterthis and Dick Whittington and His Cat, 1969-1973, undated (Box 24, Folder 376)
  - SA1058
    - Kidnapped, 1969, 1984, undated (Box 24, Folder 377)
    - Plus various other SA numbers, 1984–1986 (Box 24, Folder 378)
  - SA1059: Swiss Family Robinson, 1969, 1984, undated (Box 24, Folder 379)
  - SA1060: Poems and Songs for Younger Children, 1970-1973, undated (Box 24, Folder 380)
  - SA1061: Poems of William Blake, 1969-1971, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 381)
  - SA1062: Poems of D. H. Lawrence, 1970-1983, undated (Box 24, Folder 382)
  - SA1063: Conquerico, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 383)
    Read by Lucienne Meriaux Widmer.
  - SA1064: Hughes, Langston, 1969–1973 (Box 25, Folder 384)
  - SA1065: Kim, 1969, 1985, undated (Box 25, Folder 385)
  - SA1066: Around the World in 80 Days, 1969, 1985, undated (Box 25, Folder 386)
  - SA1068: Day-Lewis, Cecil, 1968–1971 (Box 25, Folder 387)
  - SA1070: Brer Rabbit, 1968–1970 (Box 25, Folder 388)
  - SA1093: Stories by Isaac Babel, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 389)
  - SA1100: The Pleasures of Poetry - Manuscript, circa 1981
    - pp. 1-60 (Box 25, Folder 390)
    - pp. 61-121 (Box 25, Folder 391)
    - pp. 122-183 (Box 25, Folder 392)
    - pp. 183-241 (Box 25, Folder 393)
    - pp. 242-301 (Box 26, Folder 394)
    - pp. 302-324 (Box 26, Folder 395)
  - SA1102: Someone Could Win a Polar Bear, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 396)
  - SA1104: Hawthorne, Nathaniel - King Midas and the Golden Touch, undated (Box 26, Folder 397)
  - SA1105: Hawthorne, Nathaniel -The Chimaera, undated (Box 26, Folder 398)
  - SA1114: Pablo Neruda, 1971-1972, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 399)
  - SA1126: American Ballads and Folksongs, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 400)
  - SA1127: Murder in the Rue Morgue, 1974–1986 (Box 26, Folder 401)
  - SA1129: The Facts in the Case of M. Valdemar, 1977–1986 (Box 26, Folder 402)
  - SA1130: The Black Cat, 1984–1987 (Box 26, Folder 403)
  - SA1131
    - The Puloined Letter, 1977–1986 (Box 26, Folder 404)
    - Plus various other SA numbers, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 405)
  - SA1132: Eskimo Tales, 1976–1986 (Box 26, Folder 406)
    Told by Diane Wolkstein.
  - SA1133-SA1134: Heroes of the Greek Myths, 1974-1987, undated (Box 26, Folder 407)
  - SA1135
  - Descent into the Maelstrom, 1974, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 408)
  - Plus various other SA numbers, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 409)
  - SA1136: Treasury of Spanish Folk Songs, 1975-1987, undated (Box 26, Folder 410)
  - SA1137: Treasury of Spanish Folk Songs, 1975, undated (Box 26, Folder 411)
  - SA1138: The U.N. Resolution on Racism, 1975–1976
    - 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 412)
    - 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 413)
  - SA1139: Treasury of Animal Stories, 1985, undated (Box 27, Folder 414)
    Set 2.
  - SA1140: Jong, Erica, 1975–1976 (Box 27, Folder 415)
  - SA1141: The Entebbe Answer, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 416)
  - SA1142: Jordan, June, 1974–1986 (Box 27, Folder 417)
  - SA1142: Jordan, June, 1976–1978
    - 1 of 2 (Box 27, Folder 418)
    - 2 of 2 (Box 27, Folder 419)
  - SA1144: Paley, Grace, 1974–1985 (Box 27, Folder 420)
  - SA1145-SA1151: American Jewish Poets, 1974–1982 (Box 27, Folder 421)
  - SA1153: Singer, Isacc Bashevis, 1978–1980 (Box 27, Folder 422)
  - SA1154: Koch, Kenneth, 1980–1981 (Box 27, Folder 423)
  - SA1155: Nuclear Holocaust, 1979–1980
    - Caldicott, Dr. Helen (Box 27, Folder 424)
    - Production materials (Box 28, Folder 425)
    - Contracts (Box 28, Folder 426)
  - SA1156: An Encounter with Carmen Conde, 1981-1982, undated (Box 28, Folder 427)
  - SA1157: Two Soldiers, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 428)
  - SA1158: The Language of Men, 1972–1984 (Box 28, Folder 429)
  - SA1159: The Sentinel, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 430)
  - SA1161: The Poems of Paul Ramsey, 1983–1984
    - Folder 1 (Box 28, Folder 431)
    - Folder 2 (Box 28, Folder 432)
  - SA1162: Bettelheim, Bruno, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 433)
  - SA1163: American Folk Songs for Children
    - 1 of 2, 1971, 1986, undated (Box 28, Folder 434)
    - 2 of 2, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 435)
    - Teacher's guide, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 436)
  - SA1164-SA1166, 1985–1986
    - Ozick - Rosa (Box 28, Folder 437)
    - Packing slips (Box 28, Folder 438)
  - SA1164-SA1167: Rosa - Doris Lessing, 1985–1986 (Box 28, Folder 439)
  - SA1168: Gordimer, Nadine, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 440)
  - SA1170: Ragan, Sam, 1986, undated
    - 1 of 2 (Box 29, Folder 441)
    - 2 of 2 (Box 29, Folder 442)
    - Booklet (Box 29, Folder 443)
  - SA1171: Moss, Howard, 1986–1987 (Box 29, Folder 444)
  - SA1172: Velveteen Rabbit, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 445)
  - SA1173-SA1174: Perrault, Charles, Contes de, 1986–1987 (Box 29, Folder 446)
  - SA1175-SA1176: Sacks, Oliver, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 447)
  - SA1177: Markham, Beryl, 1987
    - 1 of 2 (Box 29, Folder 448)
    - 2 of 2 (Box 29, Folder 449)
  - SA1185: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 450)
  - SA1500: Kennedy, John Fitzgerald - Production, 1960, 1972, undated (Box 29, Folder 451)
  - SA1201: Facing the Challenge of a New Age - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1991 (Box 29, Folder 452)
  - SA [PCC] 3041: Fraley, Pat, 1989–1991 (Box 29, Folder 453)
- Program guides and related materials, Series II
  Series is arranged in alphabetical order.
  - African Folk Songs: SA1163, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 454)
  - Cassette Covers: SAC1196, SAC1197, SAC4001, SAC4003, undated (Box 30, Folder 455)
  - Classic American Short Stories, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 456)
  - Composer Series, undated (Box 30, Folder 457)
  - French Drama Series, undated (Box 30, Folder 458)
  - French Language Material, undated
    - 1 of 2 (Box 30, Folder 459)
    - 2 of 2 (Box 30, Folder 460)
      Includes 2 oversizes.
  - Golden Treasury Series
    - 1 of 2, undated (Box 30, Folder 461)
    - 2 of 2, 1962, undated (Box 30, Folder 462)
  - Inaugural Addresses: Roosevelt, Franklin D. and Nixon, Richard Milhous, undated (Box 30, Folder 463)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958, undated (Box 30, Folder 464)
  - Poetry, 1981-1986, undated (Box 30, Folder 465)
  - Reading scripts, undated (Box 30, Folder 466)
  - Spanish language materials, 1962-1963, undated (Box 31, Folder 467)
  - Study Guides, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 468)
  - Teacher's guides
    - 1 of 2, 1970-1971, undated (Box 31, Folder 469)
    - 2 of 2, 1971-1972, undated (Box 31, Folder 470)
- Promotional materials and miscellaneous office records, Series III
  - Book Jackets: PCC1-PCC51, undated (Box 31, Folder 471)
  - Book Jackets: PCC63-PCC76, and unnumbered, 1987, undated (Box 31, Folder 472)
  - Catalogues, 1995, undated (Box 31, Folder 473)
  - GFI Printing Corp: SA2001, plus various other SA numbers, 1981–1982 (Box 31, Folder 474)
  - Jacket Cards
    - SA1-SA32, undated (Box 31, Folder 475)
    - SA43-1-SA57-4, 1968, 1983-1984, undated (Box 31, Folder 476)
    - SA204-SA224, SA434, 1983–1987 (Box 31, Folder 477)
    - SA701-SA799, 1969–1988 (Box 31, Folder 478)
    - SA801-SA899, 1962-1987, undated (Box 31, Folder 479)
    - SA904-SA999, 1983-1987, undated (Box 32, Folder 480)
    - SA1000-SA1098, 1969-1986, undated (Box 32, Folder 481)
    - SA1101-SA1201, 1979-1991, undated (Box 32, Folder 482)
    - SA3050, SA6514B, SA7001-SA7202, 1983-1987, undated (Box 32, Folder 483)
    - SA7500-1-SA7500-31, undated (Box 32, Folder 484)
    - SA8005-SA8050, 1983, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 485)
  - Kelly, Eamon, 1959–1960 (Box 32, Folder 486)
  - Lieberson, Goddard, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 487)
  - Lists, invoices and related material on minikits and SA numbers
    - 1 of 2, 1985-1986, undated (Box 32, Folder 488)
    - 2 of 2, 1985–1987 (Box 32, Folder 489)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, photographs and related material, 1964-1974, undated (Box 32, Folder 490)
- Artist contracts, Series IV
  Series is arranged by SAC number, with unnumbered or multi-numbered materials at the beginning of the series.
  - Royalties for Kiplinger Cassettes, 1981–1982 (Box 33, Folder 491)
    Includes 6503A-D, 6504A-C, 6505A-D, 6506A-D, SA/SAC2026, SA/SAC2033, and SA/SAC2007. Payable to A.P. Watt (Sold in England).
  - B'nai B'rith Contract, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 492)
  - Spoken Arts/Hillel Foundation Language Arts Collection, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 493)
    No royalty.
  - SAC43-1: Lolita and Poems - Smith/Skolnik, 1964, 1975-1998 (Box 33, Folder 494)
  - SAC43-3: Caldwell, Erskine - McIntosh and Otis Inc., 1973–1998 (Box 33, Folder 495)
  - SAC45-2: Golden Treasury of Irish Verse, 1969–1996 (Box 33, Folder 496)
  - SAC45-3: Finnegan's Wake, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 497)
  - SAC46-1 and SA751: Lennox Robinson, 1958–1960 (Box 33, Folder 498)
  - SAC46-2: Irish Ballads, 1956, 1967-1998 (Box 33, Folder 499)
  - SAC46-4: Irish Fairy Tales, 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 33, Folder 500)
  - SAC46-6: Folk Songs of Ireland, 1962–1998 (Box 33, Folder 501)
  - SAC47-2 and SAC47-5: French without Tears - Mrs. Lucienne Widmer, 1968–1998 (Box 33, Folder 502)
  - SAC47-5: Conquerico, 1969–1998 (Box 33, Folder 503)
  - SAC67-5: Enfance - Nathalie Sarraute, 1985-1998 (Box 33, Folder 504)
  - SAC101: Helicon, 1958, 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 505)
    Non-royalty contract.
  - SAC202: Pritchard, Robert (pianist), 1962, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 506)
  - SAC203: Steel Band, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 507)
  - SAC205: Chinese Folk Songs, 1962-1971, 1991-1998 (Box 33, Folder 508)
  - SAC213: Chansons de la Vieille France, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 509)
  - SAC223 and SAC224: A Child's Introduction to American Folk Songs, 1970–1998 (Box 33, Folder 510)
  - SAA481 and SAA482: Boys' Clubs of America, 1963–1968 (Box 33, Folder 511)
  - SAC702 - Uses of History/Our Heritage of History: Preston Slosson, 1956, 1977-1992 (Box 34, Folder 512)
  - SAC704: Death of a Salesman - International Creative, 1956–1998 (Box 34, Folder 513)
  - SAC705: Perelman, S.J., 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 34, Folder 514)
  - SAC711 and SAC48-1: French Verse - Jean Vilar, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 515)
  - SA712: Catholic Verse, 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 34, Folder 516)
  - SAC713: The Care and Feeding of the Mind, 1956, 1967-1992 (Box 34, Folder 517)
  - SAC:714: The Promise of Education, 1956, 1968-1992 (Box 34, Folder 518)
  - SAC715 and SAC48-6: French Drama, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 519)
  - SAC717: Blitzstein, Marc - Cradle will Rock, Regina, and No for an Answer, 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 34, Folder 520)
  - SAC719: Is Abraham's Bosom Roll Sweet Chariot, 1956, 1968-1989 (Box 34, Folder 521)
  - SAC722: Folk Tales of the Southwest - J. Frank Dobie, 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 34, Folder 522)
  - SAC723: Scenes from Shakespeare, 1956, 1971-1998 (Box 34, Folder 523)
  - SAC724: Wilde, Oscar, 1956, 1966-1992 (Box 34, Folder 524)
  - SAC726: Informal Hour with Dorothy Parker, 1956, 1969-1998 (Box 34, Folder 525)
  - SAC729 and SAC704: Shakespeare Sonnets - International Creative, 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 34, Folder 526)
  - SAC732: Piccoli, 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 34, Folder 527)
  - SAC735: The Size and Nature of the Universe, 1957, 1968-1998 (Box 34, Folder 528)
  - SAC741 & SAC7127: Dickens Duets, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 529)
  - SAC743 and SAC8046: Works of Synge, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 530)
  - SAC742: The Midnight Court, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 531)
  - SAC744 and SAC45-6: Golden Treasury of James Stephens, 1956-1958, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 532)
    Non-royalty contract [?].
  - SAC745: Gaelic Songs, 1967–1998 (Box 34, Folder 533)
  - SAC746: Poems of Lenore G. Marshall, 1957, 1968-1992 (Box 34, Folder 534)
  - SAC747: Poems of Richard Wilbur, 1957, 1968-1998 (Box 34, Folder 535)
  - SAC748: Raggle Taggle Gypsy Tales, 1957-1992 (Box 35, Folder 536)
  - SAC750: Subsequent, 1958, 1967-1980 (Box 35, Folder 537)
  - SAC753: Poems of William Butler Yeats, 1957, 1965-1998 (Box 35, Folder 538)
  - SAC754: Love Poems of Robert Burns, 1959, 1968-1998 (Box 35, Folder 539)
  - SAC756: Poems from Dr. Zhivago - Mrs. Tatiana Pobers Slonim, 1959, 1968-1998 (Box 35, Folder 540)
  - SAC757: Psalms and Ecclesiates, 1959, 1968-1998 (Box 35, Folder 541)
  - SAC759: Thomas, Norman: Norman Thomas Reminisces, 1959, 1968-1998 (Box 35, Folder 542)
  - SAC760: Irish Folk Songs and Ballads, 1959, 1968-1997 (Box 35, Folder 543)
  - SAC761: Emily Dickenson, 1959–1960 (Box 35, Folder 544)
  - SAC763: Invitation to Art, 1967–1992 (Box 35, Folder 545)
  - SAC764: Golden Treasury of Neval, Bandelaire, Verlaine, and Rimbaud - Disques Lucien Ades, 1959, 1968-1998 (Box 35, Folder 546)
  - SAC766 and SAC767: Scenes from Nine Shakespeare Plays, 1959, 1967-1992 (Box 35, Folder 547)
  - SAC768: Milton - Keats, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 548)
  - SAC769 and SAC46-3: Irish Fireside Stories, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 549)
  - SAC771: Italian Verse, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 550)
  - SAC772: American Verse, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 551)
  - SAC773 and SAC774: Invitation to Hebrew - Dr. Mordecai Kamrat - B'nai B'rith, 1968–1992 (Box 35, Folder 552)
  - SAC775: Conquest of Space - Curtis Brown, 1960–1993 (Box 35, Folder 553)
  - SAC776 and SAC777: Psalms - Carnovsky, Morris, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 554)
  - SAC778: Mark Twain, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 555)
  - SAC779, SAC798, SAC799, SA800, SA805 and PCC66-5: Draper, Ruth, 1975–2000 (Box 35, Folder 556)
  - SAC781, SAC782, SAC783, and SAC784: Hamlet, Macbeth, Othelo, and King Lear, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 557)
  - SAC786: Courteline, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 558)
  - SAC787 and SAC47-6: French Fairy Tales - Contes de Perrault, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 559)
  - SAC793, SAC57-1, and SAC57-2: Moliere Tartuffe, 1960–1961 (Box 35, Folder 560)
  - SAC795, SAC796, SAC797, SAC48-2, SAC48-3, and SAC48-4: French Prose I, II, and III, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 561)
  - SAC801 and SAC764: Golden Treasury Apollinaire, Cocteau, Elvard, And Aragon - Disques Lucien Ades, 1966–1998 (Box 35, Folder 562)
  - SAC802 and SAC803: Dictees Francaises Paris, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 563)
  - SAC806, SAC807, and SAC7033: Lincoln-Sandburg, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 564)
  - SAC809, SAC810, SAC7007, and SAC7009: Julius Caesar and Merchant of Venice, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 565)
  - SAC811: German Prose - Schnitzler, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 566)